The other thing
The
we'd like to
other
thing
we'd
like
to
is these companies
is
these
companies
their the
their
companies that
the
companies
that
are emerging
are
their is
emerging
their
is
astonishing Tether
astonishing
for example last
Tether
for
example
last
year we believe
year
we
believe
delivered 50 million
delivered
million
per employee
per
employee
That is unheard
That
of unheard
is
unheard
of
But we think
But
that capitalizing
we
think
that
capitalizing
on all of
on
these new
all
of
these
new
technologies is going
technologies
to drive productivity
is
going
to
drive
productivity
gains much higher
gains
than people can
much
higher
than
people
can
even postulate
even
right now
postulate
right
now
And with that
And
while many people
with
that
while
many
people
are afraid the
are
movement and
afraid
the
movement
and
AI everyone being
AI
thrown out of
everyone
being
thrown
out
of
we disagree We
we
think this is
disagree
We
think
this
is
to be one
to
of the opportunities
be
one
of
the
opportunities
for the
for
entrepreneurial spirit
the
entrepreneurial
spirit
in history
in
history